bridalguide.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy BridalGuide

BridalGuide.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy while you are on our site. The following privacy policy describes what personal information we collect from you and exactly how we use it.

BridalGuide.com is owned and operated by RFP Corp. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#87e4f2f4f3e8eae2f5f4e2f5f1eee4e2c7e5f5eee3e6ebe0f2eee3e2a9e4e8ea).

 **What information will you be asked to provide?**  
There are four different types of content on BridalGuide.com, and each has a different level of information requested. All are completely free to users.

  1. All articles and tips included on bridalguide.com are completely accessible to all users. You are not required to enroll as a member or to identify yourself in any way.
  2. Use of our message boards does not require membership to read messages. If you choose to write and post a message, you will be asked to register with a valid email address. You will also be asked to identify yourself with a user name. You may use your real name, or if you prefer anonymity you may post under a 'handle' or alias. We will not reveal your real name along with your online 'handle', but we may publish posts with real first-name-only attributions in the magazine. In addition, if you violate our posted message board rules, we may contact you privately.
  3. From time to time, we may offer special advertiser-sponsored promotions such as sweepstakes or special discounts. Any additional information you provide as part of an advertising promotion may be provided directly to the sponsoring advertiser. These will be clearly marked as promotions so you can decide whether you want to share your personal information.
  4. In addition to the content on the site, you may choose to sign up for our free weekly email newsletter, which includes planning tips and site highlights. To receive the newsletter you must provide us with a valid email address. You can choose to remove yourself from our newsletter mailing list at any time by following the 'Unsubscribe' directions printed at the end of each newsletter email.

 **How will BridalGuide.com use the information we collect?**  
First and foremost, we will use the information we collect to improve your user experience. We do this by monitoring the number of visits to each area of the site in order to determine what kind of information our users find most useful and which areas we need to enhance. This kind of evaluation is based exclusively on aggregate traffic, not on individual users—in other words, we watch to see how many users overall visit a particular article or area each week, but we do not examine specifically what any individual user reads.

Additionally, we may choose to share that aggregate traffic information with advertisers and sponsors. BridalGuide.com is completely free to users; in order to keep it that way, we need to provide advertisers with evidence that their promotions are being seen by the guaranteed number of users. We do not disclose any personally identifying information about users, and we will never provide any third party with your contact information unless you have given us permission to during the enrollment process.

We may also disclose information about our users if that disclosure is ever required by law.

 **How will BridalGuide.com collect that information?**  
There are two types of technical methods we'll use to collect information to be used in the aggregate. The first is the "cookie." This is a harmless type of data file, which we'll automatically send to your hard drive when you visit so we can recognize you on future visits to the site. Cookies cannot get information from your hard drive against your will, send you viruses or destroy files. Most browsers will allow you to change your settings to refuse cookies, or to warn you before one is accepted—but please be aware that refusing a cookie from bridalguide.com may make you unable to use certain areas of the site. (Please note that our advertisers or other sites we link to may set their own cookies or may collect personally identifiable information about you if you follow a link or ad to their site. The information practices of those websites linked to from BridalGuide.com are not covered by this privacy statement.)

Second, we will automatically log certain details about each user's computer, including the IP address (your computer's unique signature), operating system, browser software, Internet service provider, and general geographic location. As with traffic patterns, this computer information will only be used in the aggregate, to give us a broad picture of where our users are visiting from. We will not try to associate an IP address with a particular user.

Data Protection Impact Assessments (DPIA) – We have implemented documentation processes that record each assessment, allow us to rate the risk posed by the processing activity and implement mitigating measures to reduce the risk posed to the data subject(s).

Processor Agreements – where we use any third-party to process personal information on our behalf, our hosting partner; Rackspace has drafted a compliant "Processor Agreement" located at <https://www.rackspace.com/security>. These measures include initial and ongoing reviews of the services provided, the necessity of the processing activity, the technical and organizational measures in place and compliance with the GDPR.

 **What can you do to protect your personal information?**  
We will make every effort to ensure that your personal data remains secure, but you should also adopt good practices to make sure you don't inadvertently provide access to your information.

Please keep in mind that any information you provide in a message board posting becomes public, and it could be collected and used by others. BridalGuide.com can't be responsible if an outside party is able to contact you because of details you have revealed, so for your own protection, remember to use discretion in posting identifying information.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this web site, you signify your assent to the BridalGuide.com privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our web site. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time, so please check back periodically. Your continued use of the BridalGuide.com following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes.

Use of this site constitutes acceptance of our User Agreement (updated 5/25/18) and Privacy Policy and Cookie Statement (updated 5/25/18).

Note: Bridal Guide is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.
